How to sign in or log in to
your Sun Life provider account?
So, first of all, all you have to do is
download the Sun Life app on your mobile device.
Or you can also visit the Sun
Life login page on the website.
Now, inside the Sun Life app, you will see the
"Enter your credentials" option available there.
Input your Access ID and password.
Then, simply click on the
login button available there.
If you have not registered yet,
click on "Register" and follow the
prompts to create your account.
So here, as you can see, it might take a
few moments for my Sun Life account to load.
And that is it.
If you found this video helpful, please
like, share, and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you so much for watching.